(All:)Hey!
(Stuart:)What are you guys still doing here?
I got this, go. Go home.
(Howard:)You sure?
(Stuart:)Yeah, she's fed, she took her pills,
she's all tucked in and watching TV.
(Bernadette:)So, she's not too much for you?
(Stuart:)Are you kidding?
I love her, she's great.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Stewie, you gonna watch
Wheel of Fortune with me?
(Stuart:)Coming, Debbie.
(Howard:)-You call her Debbie?
-She insisted.
(Stuart:)So, hey, guys, thank you so much.
(Stuart:)This job is a dream come true.
(Howard:)Was that a little weird?
(Howard:)Yeah.
(Bernadette:)I don't know why,
but something about it feels...
(Bernadette:)...unnatural.
(Howard:)-Okay, let's go.
-Yep.
(Amy(on phone):)Okay, Sheldon,
thanks for checking in.
(Amy(on phone):)Talk to you tomorrow?
(Amy(on phone):)Okay, bye.
(Leonard:)He's okay?
(Amy:)Actually sounds like
he's doing pretty well.
(Penny:)I really think
this is gonna be for the best.
(Leonard:)Me too. And he was able
to take a sabbatical from--
How could you let him go!